The Star of Justice
No idea, darling
Oh, wait, can I get the foam on the side?
Not a problem
Appreciate it
The super ability is that they can always beat the bad guy
Do you know what that one is called?
Dodo, you can explain just as soon as I'm done working, I promise
Mom, can't you take a break now?
Dad will take care of the rest of the customers for you
It's way too much for one person alone
Hey, you're holding up the line, man
We don't got all day
What's your problem?
I'm waiting for my drink
I'm sorry, those teas will be out soon
Please, can't we play for a little bit?
You and dad have ignored me all day
I told you we shouldn't have come during rush hour
You happy?
We're gonna die of thirst
We're here, deal with it
If you entertain yourself until the rush ends
Then we'll get you a kid's meal with a toy for dinner
Thanks, here you are
Oh, why'd you have to say that?
I'm already starving, let's go and eat now
Their business is obviously booming
It's cool that it's a family shop
But they could stand to hire more people
Great, but having more employees would cut into their profits
And even with training, the drinks might not taste any better
I'm still waiting on a hibiscus green tea over here
How long's the way?
White ice
What flavor is your diet?
Oh, yeah
It's good, no?
I love it
Mom, just play with me
Here
Want to watch cartoons on my phone?
Yes!
Good boy
Why don't you take a seat outside?
Okay
I better watch you, villain
You're toast
No joke
I'll have to bring my girlfriend
Next time
It's not just me, evil sewer
Thanks, my friend
Star of justice
Bringing hope
Star of courage
Conquering fear
Star of wisdom
Serving knowledge
It'll be done soon
Please, hang on
Thank you, sir
Wait
Dodo
Where are you?
Sweetie?
Dodo?
What's the matter?
Our son
He's disappeared
Dodo
Son
Greatest selfishness
Shall be your downfall
Solo
It didn't take too long to realize
Something has changed in the back of my mind
Your eyes
There ain't nowhere left to hide behind
Time no longer flew like it was
When the flash froze everything before
Without you
I don't know if I could take this road
And I'm about to lose my mind
Every minute that I die
Back in time
Every single day
Existence rewinds
Some physical pain in this eye
Drive
All mine
All the heartache
And the smile's never faded
I know you'll be by my side
When we make it
Come back from the times
Back in time
Dive back in time
Since that night
Lou and I haven't really talked much
I don't understand
What was the point of delivering all those messages
If we didn't end up saving anyone
Listen
You know the rules
We go to the past
But we leave it like we found it
Don't question what's happened
Or the future will be altered
Because of us
I have to admit
At first I thought the whole
Diving into photos thing
Would be easy
No sweat
I'll follow your instructions
You say jump
And I jump
Simple as that
I'm all ears
This is actually a big deal
You know
If we work together
The debt should be paid
In no time
I'm sorry
But I need some time
Away from this
All right boys
Talk
What are you doing
Besides avoiding work
I think we need a break
Trust me
It'll end up being good for business
In the long run
And do you agree
Are you running on empty as well
Fine
Rest up
Just let me know when you're good
A guest has arrived
Excuse me
I'm looking for an old witch
Who can enter the past through photos
Nope
There's no such thing here
Definitely no one old
I'm sorry to disappoint you
I'm officer Zhao Li
Police
Huh
You don't seem thrilled
To have a cop here
Why would we be
The police showing up unannounced
Is almost never a good thing
Wouldn't you have a similar reaction
Given that the roles were reversed
We're just your average business
There's no time travel here
I think you better watch your hands
Sorry sir
She can be a lot
Please leave
We don't want the neighbors
Thinking we're up to no good
You understand
All right
That's enough
I'll see myself out
Please miss
You have to help me
I'll do anything you want
You see
I heard that somebody here
Can look into the past
Please do that for me
Help me find my lost son
He went missing three years ago
There are no clues
Despite everything this officer
And his people have done for me
But I know
He's alive
I'm sorry
But they've already said
That what you read
Was merely a rumor
You've been scanned
By several con artists already
You just don't have more money to lose
Listen
I promise
As long as I'm on the force
I'll keep this case active
Whatever it takes
We won't stop
I have faith he's out there
I know one day I'll hug my son again
I won't give up
Purchase this jade turtle from me
Place it at your window
And this part's important
Put scissors underneath it
In less than six months
You'll have your kid back
Dodo
Forgive me
I'm so sorry
My son
Please come back to us
I shouldn't have let you watch cartoons alone
It's your daddy's fault
I'm the one to blame
Please sir
Let me help you up
It's tough
I can't imagine
But this is just a regular photo studio though
Begging won't do you any good
Listen
He's right
But if you have any old pictures you want printed
You can bring them here
We'll do it for free
You can't go to the past
Best if you give up on that dream
What's happened has happened
Nothing can change that
Live your life
Be present
Move on
When the courier shows up
Give him this for me
Leong
This boy's words may be harsh for you to hear
But he's not wrong
Your wife needs you
Come on
Let's go
Is she doing any better these days?
You can't feed me alone
It's not just me
Evil doer
Face my friends
Star of justice
Bringing hope
Star of courage
Conquering fear
Star of wisdom
Darling
Do you know what the star of justice's strongest power is?
Go on and guess
No idea
But dear
Earlier today
We found a promising new clue
We might see Dodo soon
Come on
Take a guess
Here
I'll give you a hint
The special power that always takes the bad guy down
Okay
Let me think
Soaring skyball
Uh-uh
Banishing light
Nope
Try again
Then you're gonna have to tell me
Are you positive you don't know?
It's the heart of hope
Beware the power of justice
Evil we will defeat you
Here
You're welcome for bringing you the surprise milk tea
I'm in your debt
Researching?
Oh
Is there any news about the kid?
No
Nothing unfortunately
Ever since we heard that he went missing
I've been curious to know what happened
That's good
It sounds like you're getting back to your old self
But why were you so cold to Mr. Liang?
The poor man already feels terrible
One more
Go ahead and finish the last bite
I have to tell you
I saw him before
Three years ago
Let's get you cleaned up
There was this milk tea shop close to my school that was blowing up
I consulted a specialist
Tuesday at 8 a.m. is the best time for us to open
It'll make us a success
Oh yeah?
You didn't fall for another trick, did you?
Let me see the little guy
Take a break
Come here
The same specialist picked out Dodo's name
And he's absolutely perfect
Isn't that right?
Thought so
It was so tragic
They had just opened
Then he went missing
Oh good, the rain stopped
I'll put up more of the missing flyers
So why don't you stay right here and watch some more of your cartoons
Does that sound good?
Mm-hmm
How perfect!
I can destroy you all at once
Now prepare to meet your doom!
Afterward, I saw him on the streets around the school a lot
He and his wife posted countless flyers
I can't imagine the toll
Excuse me, but would you look at this?
Have you seen him anywhere?
Take it
If you remember anything, please let us know at once
I'm sorry
I've never seen your child
I wanted to tell him the truth so badly
But
I lied instead
See, I had seen a son before
Walking with someone else
The day he disappeared
I've always regretted that I didn't ask any questions
Like, why is this child with you?
I was terrified that I'd run into Mr. Liang again
How was I supposed to face him?
Everywhere I went
I saw the boy's face
After graduating, I avoided the area as much as I could
I thought I could escape those hives
However
Even after three long years
His father never lost hope
All I want is to fix my mistake
So, please, help them for me
Our dodo is perfect, isn't it?
Okay, I will
My way of saying thanks
For getting me milk tea in the rain
Oh, well
I'm not the one who bought these
But thanks
Appreciate the drink
Wait, I don't have his contact info
Yes, hello
What?
Really?
Amazing
You're certain?
Great
Thanks so much
Why am I not able to crack this case?
Hey, Chunbin, the page about the seventh victim isn't in the file
Hello?
You out there?
Where did that kid run off to?
Hey, Chunbin, did you even open this case file?
It's missing important info
Hold on
Leong did what?
Yeah
He was after some old surveillance footage
Said it would help him see the past
I told you
I'm not allowed to make random copies unless it's authorized
I had just figured that if you intended to help, I'd take the initiative
So here I am
Yeah, all right
Just make it quick
What's his new angle?
Thought we cleared up those internet rumors
Just this once
Could you make an exception and cut some footage together for me?
Thanks
Not so fast, kid
That surveillance video is hours long
How do you expect me to know what you want?
You do it
Just send, like, a clip
A video of the past
Top secret video
This is strictly for internal use
Do not forward it to anyone
Got that?
Hey, Leong, I got you that surveillance footage
Oh, and by the way, it's for your eyes only
No sharing
Miss Chao
This is video from the day of the incident
I hope it will help you find some clues
Thank you again for your help
Really
This came from a friend at the station
Don't show anyone else
This video is important
Don't send it to our resident Loudmouth, yeah?
Why is she calling me out?
Forward it to me
I'll totally keep my lips sealed
No chance
Dota was sitting in a blind spot
At least there's no footage that we've been able to track down
Do you happen to remember when he went missing?
Yes, midday
It was sweltering out
Business was really good
Dota wanted his mom to play with him
But she was swamped
I gave him my phone
I'm not sure when that was
We were slammed
But at one point, I looked at the clock
It was around three
More like 250
Not long after
My wife realized he was gone
Okay, so
When you use your ability on this video
What do you actually see?
Twelve hours of surveillance footage from cameras
Within a one kilometer radius
But I can't see anything a camera didn't pick up
Have you spotted the kid yet?
Who was with him?
Someone quite smart
They must have planned this in advance
They stayed in the blind spots
I couldn't make out anything helpful
Which means
You'll still need to dive in
When I go in a picture
I turn into the photographer
If I use a video
Will I become
A surveillance camera?
Seriously?
You idiot
Just follow my lead
A large black milk tea
Ice
Light sugar
Nuts to go?
It'll be just a moment
Thanks
Huh?
Wait
How did I end up here as myself?
This is three years in the past, right?
You've got half a day to explore
Be smart
Keep a low profile
Like you were never there
Don't change things
And do not attract attention
Hey, what are you doing?
Look and see if you can find Dodo
I'm being stealthy
Playing by the rules
Nobody looks too suspicious
Why don't I just...
You know why I agreed to the earthquake mission?
I obviously knew those messages
Wouldn't save anyone from dying
But they did help someone who survived
Live with less regret
He's gone!
Where are they?
Try the next alley
Oh, let's check out the shop
Maybe the line isn't too long yet
Yeah, sure
Stop!
Turn back!
Hey, it's you
Can't have a
Let me be
Huh?
Wait
What are you doing here?
I got lost in the street that I'm living in
Or maybe I should just quit overthinking
I should stop thinking about it
Stop thinking about it
Stop stop thinking about it
While your mind overclouded
脱离现实的梦境化为寂寞
始终的我需要怎样才能自保
So stop thinking about it
Stop thinking about it
Why your mind overclouded
在这时间的风险停止思考
我明白多少烦恼都是永恒自柔
Stop thinking about it
Why your mind overclouded
Yeah
O